Tvler Wolf

Tampa, FL | (813) 344-9398 | wolfptyler@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Florida Atlantic University, Boca Raton, FL

Bachelor in Business Administration, Marketing

May 2021

SUMMARY

As a Florida Atlantic University graduate with a degree in Business Administration and a focus on Marketing, I am excited to bring my skills and knowledge to a challenging and rewarding role. My experience as a Social Media Manager, Marketing Coordinator, and Marketing Assistant has given me a solid foundation in managing marketing campaigns, analyzing data, and creating effective content. I am proficient in tools such as Excel, SQL, Power BI, Tableau, and Google Analytics, and have completed a Google Data Analytics Specialization Certificate to further enhance my skills in data analysis.

TECHNICAL SKILLS AND CONTINUED EDUCATION

- Focused my post-graduate education on data analytics through DataCamp, Google courses, and other educational materials.
- Google Data Analytics Specialization Certificate.
- SQL, Excel (data cleaning, visualizations, pivot table, etc.), Power BI, Google Analytics, Facebook Ads Manager.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Omni Advertising, Boca Raton, FL

Nov. 2021 - Present

Social Media Manager

- Manages a budget of \$12,000 for Facebook advertising, with a focus on achieving important levels of CPC and CTR through strategic A/B testing.
- Leverages data insights to design and implement effective social media campaigns. Including monitoring, analyzing, and communicating KPIs from Facebook and Google Analytics to optimize campaign performance and drive business results.
- Maintains a CRM database to facilitate customer and dealership communication. Additionally, responsible for analyzing survey data and providing valuable data to stakeholders and business units.
- Creates content for more than thirty automotive dealerships in the southeast region.
- Attends weekly meetings about opportunities and strategies for achieving organizational goals.

Daystrom Edge | TBT Holdings, Boca Raton, FL

Aug. 2021 – Oct. 2021

Marketing Coordinator

- Applied market analysis and identify real estate trends to locate profitable properties that met the needs of potential customers within a \$3,000,000 budget.
- Created strategic visualizations for reporting data, including dashboards and reports, using Excel to create projections and visualizations for presentations to management.
- Developed and implemented paid search and SEO strategies, provided insights and reporting for an affiliate marketing campaign to drive success and maximize ROI, and created a comprehensive keyword database using Google's data for lead generation and affiliated marketing efforts.

Reatro Ventures, Boca Raton, FL

Marketing Assistant

Dec. 2020 - Jul. 2021

- Presented results of marketing campaigns and social media statistics to clients monthly, providing valuable insights for decision-making and strategy planning.
- Governed the collection of data, creative assets, and press contacts.
- Led the production, execution, and evaluation of email advertising campaigns.